[
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1201_Watcher_Death",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1201_Watcher_Death_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1201_Watcher_Death_Response"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1201_Watcher_Corruption",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1201_Watcher_Corruption_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1201_Watcher_Corruption_Response"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1202_Magistrate_Monarchs",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Magistrate_Monarchs_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1202_Magistrate_Monarchs_Response"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1202_Magistrate_Factions",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Magistrate_Factions_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1202_Magistrate_Factions_Response",
		"AchievementUnlock": "S_factionchoiceready",
		"RequiredAchievement": "S_factiontalkedto"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1222_Innkeep_WhereNow",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1222_Innkeep_WhereNow_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1222_Innkeep_WhereNow_Response"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1222_Innkeep_WhyHouse",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1222_Innkeep_WhyHouse_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1222_Innkeep_WhyHouse_Response"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Survivalist1203_01",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@Survivalist1203_01_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@Survivalist1203_01_Response"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1202_Marauder_talk",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Marauder_talk_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1202_Marauder_talk_Response",
		"AchievementUnlock": "S_introtomarauders",
		"RequiredAchievement": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1202_Syndicate_talk",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Syndicate_talk_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1202_Syndicate_talk_Response",
		"AchievementUnlock": "S_introtosyndicate",
		"RequiredAchievement": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1202_Covenant_talk",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Covenant_talk_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1202_Covenant_talk_Response",
		"AchievementUnlock": "S_introtocovenant",
		"RequiredAchievement": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1202_Marauder_dye_talk",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Marauder_dye_talk_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1202_Marauder_dye_talk_Response",
		"RequiredAchievement": "S_marauderquest1"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1202_Syndicate_dye_talk",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Syndicate_dye_talk_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1202_Syndicate_dye_talk_Response",
		"RequiredAchievement": "S_syndicatequest1"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1202_Covenant_dye_talk",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Covenant_dye_talk_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1202_Covenant_dye_talk_Response",
		"RequiredAchievement": "S_covenantquest1"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1204_Constable_EncroachingCorruption",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1204_Constable_EncroachingCorruption_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1204_Constable_EncroachingCorruption",
		"AchievementUnlock": "S_encroachingconstable"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1225_Giacomo_HousingGeneral",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingGeneral_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingGeneral_Response",
		"RequiredAchievement": "S_downpayment"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1225_Giacomo_HousingStorage",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingStorage_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingStorage_Response",
		"RequiredAchievement": "12_Quest_Housing_3b"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1225_Giacomo_HousingTrophy",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingTrophy_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingTrophy_Response",
		"RequiredAchievement": "12_Quest_Housing_6"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "1223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Response"
	}
]